directvdeals.com 2017-06-22

# DIRECTVDeals.com Privacy Policy

**EFFECTIVE DATE: 11/16/15**

Welcome to Directvdeals.com. This site is controlled and operated by DirectStarTV, LLC. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and share information, as well as various options you have to control how your information is used.

**KEY TERMS**

In order to better help you understand this Privacy Policy, here are definitions for some of the key terms we use throughout. 

  * **Personally-Identifiable Information:** Personally-Identifiable Information (“PII”) refers to any information that can be used to identify a particular individual, including name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, financial account number, and government-issued identifiers. 
  * **Non-Personally-Identifiable Information:** Non-Personally-Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) refers to information about individuals that, in some cases, could serve to identify a device or browser. Non-PII, however, does not identify an individual. 
  * **Cookies:** The term “cookies” can refer to tasty treats that you eat, but when we use that term here, we are referring to small text files that can be sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies may be set by the site or its third-party service partners. Cookies can be used to keep track of things like your preferences, activities on a site, and where you left off during your last visit. The site or service that places a particular cookie has permission to read the contents of that cookie each time it communicates with your browser.
  * **Tags:** Tags (also known as pixel tags or web beacons) are like milk to the cookies, and the two work together. More specifically, tags are small blocks of code on a web page that allow websites to do things like read and place cookies. Tags can collect anonymous information, such as a visitor’s IP address, browser type, operating system, and the time the visitor reached the website. 
  * **IP Address:** An IP address (or Internet Protocol address) is an address that allows computers to identify each other and know where to send information. IP addresses can be associated with general geographic areas. Please note, though, that an IP address is not an exact physical address.
  * **Flash Cookies:** Flash cookies (or Local Shared Objects) are pieces of data that websites you visit may store on your computer. These are like the cookies described above, except that they can also store data more complex than simple text. To learn more about Flash cookies, click [here](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html).

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Reviews and Other Submissions

You may post reviews, comments, and other content to our website; send communications; and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, damaging to third parties, or otherwise objectionable, and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam." You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a submission. We reserve the right (but are not obligated) to remove or edit such content, but do not regularly review posted content.

If you do post content or submit material, and unless we indicate otherwise, you grant the operator of this website and its designees a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display any and all such submissions throughout the world in any media now known or hereafter developed. You grant the operator of this website and its designees the right to use the name you submit in connection with such submission, at their election, but you acknowledge there is no obligation to do so. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the submission; that the submission is accurate; that use of the submission does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify the operator of this website and its designees for all claims resulting from your submissions. We have the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. The operator of this website takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content submitted or posted by you or any third party.

Other Information You Provide

We also collect information from you when you choose to share it with us to use our site, create an online account with us, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, post a review, make a purchase, participate in a survey or promotion, or otherwise contact or interact with us. The information we collect may include PII and Non-PII. We may combine the information you provide to us with information (1) from and about you that we automatically collect when you use this or other first party sites, (2) from third parties (e.g., the provider of the goods or services offered on this site), or (3) from other online and offline sources.

Information Automatically Collected

We may use Cookies, Tags, IP Addresses, Flash Cookies, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to, and users of, our site, to deliver online advertisements that we think would be more relevant to your interests, and to monitor interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, through these means, we may automatically collect your browser type, operating system, IP address, software version, and the domain name from which you accessed the site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the site, the areas or pages of the site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the site, the number of times you return to the site, and other click-stream or site usage data, emails or ads that you open, forward or click-through to our site. Collecting this information, and linking it with your PII, helps us to best tailor our website and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site, and to help identify site features, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you. Additionally, we may collect online and mobile activity data when you access our mobile applications or use the browser on your mobile device to access our website.  For example, if you have enabled location services on your mobile device, we may collect geolocation data from your device, as well as unique user IC, cell phone model, operation system, and carrier. We also may use third party advertisements placed by ad networks to support our site. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as Cookies, Tags, and Flash Cookies when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers and ad networks information including your IP address, internet service provider, the browser you used to visit our site, and whether you have Adobe Flash installed. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may use data, such as demographic data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. These advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our site and on other third party sites, demographic information and/or general location, so that the advertising you see on our site more closely reflects your interests and needs. For example, if you search for a product on our site, you may see an advertisement from a third party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past. You are free to set your browser to decline Cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the “Tools” or “Help” tabs in your browser (or your mobile device privacy settings) to learn how to change your Cookie and other tracking preferences. Note that our systems do not recognize Do Not Track headers from browsers. You can also opt-out of receiving personalized ads from us and other third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising using their respective opt-out tools. You can find the NAI’s opt-out tool [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the DAA’s opt out tool [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). These opt-out tools are Cookie-based. Please note that these tools will not prevent all collection of data on the browser on which they are installed, will only function if your browser is set to accept third-party Cookies, and may not be as reliable in cases where Cookies are sometimes automatically disabled or removed (such as on certain mobile devices). As long as you don’t delete the opt-out Cookie, its opt-out function will work for up to ten years. However, if you delete an opt-out Cookie from a browser’s Cookie files, data collection from that browser will resume until an opt-out Cookie is reset on that browser. You can opt out of interest-based ads from Google by following the steps located [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en). For more information about opting out of custom audience advertisements on Facebook click [here](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/1415256572060999). For more information about your privacy controls and tailored ads on Twitter click [here](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170407?lang=en). 

INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM OTHER SOURCES

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, email address, unique device identifiers, and publicly-observed data, such as from online activity, social media and shopping behavior. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.

**Information Use**

  * We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:
  * To fulfill orders, provide service, and communicate with customers;
  * To research and develop new products or services;
  * To respond to your inquiries;
  * To provide you and other users with customized site content, targeted offers, and advertising on the site, on other sites, or via email;
  * To customize ads on third party sites, including but not limited to Facebook, Google, and Twitter;
  * To contact you when necessary;
  * To review the usage and operations of our site and improve our content, products, and services;
  * To address problems with the site or our business;
  * To promote the site;
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of the site and our business;
  * As described to you at the point of data collection; and
  * To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.

**Email**

If we send you an email advertisement, it will include instructions on how to opt out of receiving such emails in the future.  If you are a customer and you elect to opt out of receiving email advertisements, you may still receive emails about your account relationships. 

**Information Disclosure**

We may disclose the personal information we collect from and about you as follows: (1) to the service provider that operates this site and its affiliated companies; (2) to other service providers if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement or regulatory agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) to third parties offering products or services on this site; (6) to other select third parties that we believe may have offers of interest to you; (7) to promote the site and our business to third parties; and (8) as described to you at the point of collection. We may also share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties. Also, we may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to obtain the transferee’s agreement to use personal information provided through this site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us in writing at Attn: Privacy Policy Maintenance- 1101 Red Ventures Drive, Fort Mill, SC 29707.

**Links to Other Websites**

The site may have links to third-party websites or applications, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites or applications.

**Children’s Information**

This site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 should provide information to our site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use, provide information, make purchases, use any of the interactive or public features of this site, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may have.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

**If You Have Questions**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at 704-971-2300.

**Revisions to This Statement**

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the policy. We will indicate the policy’s effective date on the first page.

<https://mixpanel.com/optout>. Customer agrees to provide appropriate notices to its Authorized Users about, and if required by applicable laws obtain appropriate consent from such Authorized Users for, Customer’s information collection and use practices relating to Customer’s use of the Application Services and Customer’s use of cookies for tracking purposes. Appropriate notices may include notice in the form of a privacy policy posted on Customer’s site, in Customer’s mobile application, and/or, if Customer uses Mixpanel Notifications (as discussed in further detail below), in the emails Customer sends through the Application Services. Customer also agrees to include a notice about the Mixpanel opt-out for Customer’s site and the Mixpanel opt-out link in Customer’s privacy policy or in a notice on Customer’s Website(s). Customer will also inform its Authorized Users that if they get a new computer, install a new browser, erase or otherwise alter their browser's cookie file (including upgrading certain browsers) they may also clear the Mixpanel opt-out cookie.
